

HUY LE JULY 9. 2000

EXECUTIVE PROFILE

I am currently a student at RMIT University with strong communication and interpersonal skills. A motivated employee with an excellent track record in working autonomously as well as part of a larger team. Having proven experience in meeting deadlines and high involvement in integration projects. Highly organized and skilled in managing different tasks simultaneously. Passionate and committed in work approach.

PROFESSIONAL SKILLS

- MS Excel (intermediate) · MS Word · MS PowerPoint, MS Outlook
- Excellent communication and interpersonal skills
- Ability to prioritize and perform multiple tasks simultaneously
- · Outstanding customer service skills
- Ability to work effectively individually and with a team
- Able to spend more time to finish the job
- Ability to follow oral and written instructions
- · Fluent English communication

CONTACT INFORMATION:

• Telephone: +84935507182

• Email: lehuy972000@gmail.com

829 Huynh Tan Phat Street, Phu Thuan Ward, District 7, Ho Chi Minh city

CAREER HISTORY

Community Center in Berryville, AR, USA 601 Dr Spurlin Cir, Berryville, AR 72616, USA

Job purpose(s): Cashier, helper Sep 2017 – Jan 2017

- Collecting the pieces of stuff in the gym, and picking balls on the volleyball/basketball/soccer courts
- · Being able to help the customers to register as membership
- · Helping the elders
- Reception duties: welcoming, checking in to the gym, and managing the exercise areas

Bo Go Coffee in Da Nang City, Viet Nam 220 Trung Nu Vuong, Binh Thuan Ward, Hai Chau District, Da Nang, Viet Nam

Job purpose(s): Manager, cashier, and customer service May 2018 - Aug 2018

- · Training new staffs
- Able to use the coffee machines
- Handle customers complaints and respond to the shop
- Clearing tables, taking dirty glasses/cups to the dishwasher, setting tables, and otherwise
 assisting the waiting staff.
- Responsible for cash and credit card transactions, tipping out wait staff, and balancing the register at the end of the shift.

Beyond The Bowl Restaurant in Seattle, WA, USA 12518 Lake City Way NE, Seattle, WA 98125, USA

Job purpose(s): Deputy manager, cashier, and waiter Jan 2019 - Dec 2019

- · Training new staffs
- Perform Food & Beverage (F&B) related duties such as waiters, and cleaners
- Take orders through telecommunications and food ordering apps like UberEats, Doordash, and Caviar
- Proficient in cash, debit, and credit card payment transactions
- Take care of customers at the service at the restaurant, take away and online ordering

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Phan Chau Trinh High School in Da Nang, Viet Nam 154 Le Loi Street, Hai Chau 1 Ward, Hoa Vang District, Đà Nẵng

Sep 2015 - May 2017

- Always ranked 5th in class
- Aet high marks in classes with more than 3.32 GPA

Christian Calvary Academy in Berryville, AR, USA 908 US-62 Spur, Berryville, AR 72616, USA

Sep 2017 - May 2018

Graduated with high school diploma

GPA: 4.0

South Puget Sound Community College 2011 Mottman Rd SW, Olympia, WA 98512, USA

Sep 2018- Dec 2018

- Associate of Science in Engineering Sciences
- GPA: 4.0
- Major: Mechanical Engineering

North Seattle College 9600 College Way N, Seattle, WA 98103, USA

Jan 2019 - Aug 2020

- Associate of Science in Engineering Sciences
- GPA: 3.77
- Major: Mechanical Engineering

RMIT University

702 Nguyen Van Linh Street, Tan Hung Ward, District 7, Ho Chi Minh City

July 2021 - Now

• Major: Robotics Engineering